Personal Info

Phone: 9840042253

E-mail:

santosh.neupane.0330@gmail.com

website:

santosh-neupane.com.np

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/santosh-neupane-0330

Github:

github.com/San0330

Hobbies

Cloud Technology

Full Stack Development

Reading Books

Gardening

Achievements

Achieved top 5% in LinkedIn skill assessment for JavaScript, PHP and CSS

Participated in ICPC Regional Programming Competition, Dhaka,Bangladesh

Participated in various hackathons

Hobby Projects

Advanced Programming in UNIX

 Learning About Linux from "Advanced Programming in UNIX Environment" Book.

UI Designs

 Implementing some great UIs found from design sites like dribble

Algorithms

Santosh Neupane

Software Engineer

With over 2 years of experience in IT industry, I am dedicated to creating innovative and high-performing solutions. My greatest strength is my problem solving skills, work ethics and ability to implement various software development methodologies.

EXPERIENCE

Momayo Technology

2022 - Present

Full-stack Developer

- Developed EMIS application with various modules for both university staffs and students.
- Collaborated with clients to define software requirements.
- Participated in architecture, design and implementation of backend features using Laravel, Jquery etc.
- Improved response time of application using SQL optimization technique, caching etc when generating summary reports.

Neutroline Pvt Ltd

2021 - 2022

Software Engineer Intern

- Contributed to Employee Management System.
- Integrated third-party tools and components into application.
- Refactored and improved legacy code.
- Provided guidance to new interns.
- Collaborated with management and development partners regarding software application design status and project progress

Skills

PHP/Laravel	ReactJS	My SQL
NodeJS	Git/Github	Tailwind CSS
Flutter	Docker	

EDUCATION

Master in IT 2023 - Present

Tribhuvan University, Kathmandu

Bachelor in CSIT 2016 - 2021

Nepathya College, Butwal